<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://digitalrats.ru/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://digitalrats.ru/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-09T15:58:59+05:00</updated><id>https://digitalrats.ru/feed.xml</id><title type="html">DigitalRats</title><subtitle>DigitalRats studio was founden in a memories of older team CRG.  It was a late 90s Sinclair ZX-SPECTRUM fan group im my own city.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Добро пожаловать!</title><link href="https://digitalrats.ru/en-US/jekyll/update/2020/02/09/welcome-to-digitalrats.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Добро пожаловать!" /><published>2020-02-09T14:49:50+05:00</published><updated>2020-02-09T14:49:50+05:00</updated><id>https://digitalrats.ru/en-US/jekyll/update/2020/02/09/welcome-to-digitalrats</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://digitalrats.ru/en-US/jekyll/update/2020/02/09/welcome-to-digitalrats.html">&lt;p&gt;Warning: automated translation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our blog. Here you will find articles about our projects, experiments and just lyrics.
The blog was created as a platform in order to share experience primarily for the development team
DigitalRats. Although the “team” is a little loudly said - now it consists of only one person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, I hope that designers can take advantage of this magazine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Publications can be short, like this one, more worthy of twitter or a Telegram channel, or very large and difficult to understand. How to read this? There will always be a simple static site, maybe I’ll bother with search, tag clouds and all the other fancy stuff someday, but
it will not be soon (there are no databases and full-text search engines, no nodejs or PHP on the server side). I think if you are interested in what will happen next - just follow the publications.
Someday, search engines will get to us, but for now just read the latest publication and continue to the past until you get bored.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Warning: automated translation Welcome to our blog. Here you will find articles about our projects, experiments and just lyrics. The blog was created as a platform in order to share experience primarily for the development team DigitalRats. Although the “team” is a little loudly said - now it consists of only one person. Nevertheless, I hope that designers can take advantage of this magazine. Publications can be short, like this one, more worthy of twitter or a Telegram channel, or very large and difficult to understand. How to read this? There will always be a simple static site, maybe I’ll bother with search, tag clouds and all the other fancy stuff someday, but it will not be soon (there are no databases and full-text search engines, no nodejs or PHP on the server side). I think if you are interested in what will happen next - just follow the publications. Someday, search engines will get to us, but for now just read the latest publication and continue to the past until you get bored.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Добро пожаловать!</title><link href="https://digitalrats.ru/jekyll/update/2020/02/09/welcome-to-digitalrats.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Добро пожаловать!" /><published>2020-02-09T14:49:50+05:00</published><updated>2020-02-09T14:49:50+05:00</updated><id>https://digitalrats.ru/jekyll/update/2020/02/09/welcome-to-digitalrats</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://digitalrats.ru/jekyll/update/2020/02/09/welcome-to-digitalrats.html">&lt;p&gt;Добро пожаловать в наш блог. Тут вы найдете стати о наших проектах, экспериментах и просто лирику.
Блог создан как площадка для того, чтобы делиться опытом в первую очередь для команды разработчиков
DigitalRats. Хотя “команда” это немного громко сказано - сейчас она состоит только из одного человека.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Все же, я надеюсь, что и дизайнеры смогут воспользоваться этим журналом.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Публикации могут быть короткими, как эта, более достойная twitter или канала Telegram, или очень большими и трудными для понимания. Как же это читать? Тут всегда будет простой статический сайт, возможно, я озабочусь поиском, облаками тегов и всеми прочими модными штуками когда-нибудь, но 
это будет не скоро (тут нет баз данных и движков полнотекстового поиска, нет nodejs или PHP на стороне сервера). Думаю, если вам интересно что будет дальше - просто следите за публикациями.
Когда-нибудь поисковые машины до нас доберутся, а пока просто читайте последнюю публикацию и дальше в прошлое пока не надоест.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Добро пожаловать в наш блог. Тут вы найдете стати о наших проектах, экспериментах и просто лирику. Блог создан как площадка для того, чтобы делиться опытом в первую очередь для команды разработчиков DigitalRats. Хотя “команда” это немного громко сказано - сейчас она состоит только из одного человека. Все же, я надеюсь, что и дизайнеры смогут воспользоваться этим журналом. Публикации могут быть короткими, как эта, более достойная twitter или канала Telegram, или очень большими и трудными для понимания. Как же это читать? Тут всегда будет простой статический сайт, возможно, я озабочусь поиском, облаками тегов и всеми прочими модными штуками когда-нибудь, но это будет не скоро (тут нет баз данных и движков полнотекстового поиска, нет nodejs или PHP на стороне сервера). Думаю, если вам интересно что будет дальше - просто следите за публикациями. Когда-нибудь поисковые машины до нас доберутся, а пока просто читайте последнюю публикацию и дальше в прошлое пока не надоест.</summary></entry></feed>